A Guide to the Williams C. Wooldridge papers, ca. 1960-2015
Library of Virginia
- Series III: William[2] (ca. 1709-1798) son of 1.John., Extent: 7 boxes. (Box 8-14)
  - 161. Teressa[4] daughter of 33.Thomas. (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - 34. Edward[3] son of 4.William. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - 162. ?Edward[4] son of 34.Edward. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - 565. Drusilla[5] daughter of 162.Edward; 567. Mary B. Caroline[5] daughter of 162.Edward. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - 566. Drewry[5] son of 162.Edward. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - 568. Anderson Green[5] son of 162.Edward. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - 569. David Hudspeth[5] son of 162.Edward. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - 570. Wilson Wayne[5] son of 162.Edward. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - 571. Madison Brasher[5] son of 162.Edward. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - 163. Anna[4] daughter of 34.Edward; 164. Mildred[4] daughter of 34.Edward; 165. Martha[4] daughter of 34.Edward. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - 166. John[4] son of 34.Edward. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - 573. Alpheus F.[] son of 166.John. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - 574. Erasmus[5] son of 166.John. (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - 575. John A.[5] son of 166.John. (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - 576. Edward[5] son of 166.John. (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - 577. Almeira[5] daughter of 166.John. (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - 35. Sarah Flournoy[3] daughter of 4.William; 36. Martha[3] daughter of 4.William. (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Series IV: Edward[2] (ca. 1711-1808) son of 1.John., Extent: 6 boxes. (Box 14-19)
  Edward[2] contains papers on the descendants of Edward Wooldridge (ca. 1711-1808), son of John Wooldridge (ca. 1678-1757).
  - 5. Edward Wooldridge[2] (ca. 1711-1808) son of 1.John. (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - 37. -----[3] daughter of 5.Edward (married William Hancock). (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - 38. Edward[3] son of 5.Edward. (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - 167. Edward[4] son of 38.Edward. (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - 168. Sally[4] daughter of 38.Edward; 170. Green[4] son of 38.Edward; 171. Simon[4] son of 38.Edward; 172. Althea[4] daughter of 38.Edward; 173. Martin[4] son of 38.Edward; 174. David[4] son of 38.Edward. (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - 169. Chesley[4] son of 38.Edward. (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - 580. Johnson T.[5] son of 169.Chesley. (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - 581. Edward[5] son of 169.Chesley. (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - 582. Green[5] son of 169.Chesley. (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - 583. Merritt[5] son of 169.Chesley; 584. Elizabeth[5] daughter of 169.Chesley. (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - 590. Mary T.[5] daughter of 174.David. (Box 14, Folder 27)